<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Quebecnacabeca</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 14:43:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/live-favicon.jpg</url>
	<title>Quebecnacabeca</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mana Bay Dive Into An Aquatic Wonder Just A Splash Away</title>
		<link>/mana-bay-dive-into-an-aquatic-wonder-just-a-splash-away/</link>
					<comments>/mana-bay-dive-into-an-aquatic-wonder-just-a-splash-away/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mana Bay Dive Into An Aquatic Wonder Just A Splash Away]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=512</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Embark on a journey into the aquatic wonderland of Mana Bay, where the humdrum of...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Embark on a journey into the aquatic wonderland of Mana Bay, where the humdrum of Dhaka&#8217;s urban jungle is swapped for a &#8220;splash-tastic&#8221; escape just 49.4 km away! Forget fancy restaurants; Mana Bay is your ticket to adventure! This is not your run-of-the-mill waterpark. Mana Bay is a quirky oasis crafted by a team of globetrotting thrill enthusiasts and British investment. Imagine White Water, the masterminds behind global waterpark sensations teaming up to create a tropical haven that puts the &#8220;fun&#8221; in funky!</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Mana Bay is not just about water slides – it is a day-long adrenaline rush with rides that will make butterflies flutter in your stomach (the good kind!). And the fun does not stop there; they have got tranquil cabanas, dining options that will make your taste buds dance and attractions that combine the allure of Disney&#8217;s magical realm with the thrilling pizzazz of Universal&#8217;s Volcano Bay! United, these enchanting features at Mana Bay will keep you spellbound throughout the entire adventure.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Setting the bar for excellence is their mantra! An international dream team is on duty, ensuring every aspect is crafted to perfection, allowing you to immerse yourself in the uplifting Polynesian vibes with nothing but positivity. And speaking of vibes, &#8220;Mana&#8221; in Hawaiian means spiritual energy – and trust us, it&#8217;s woven into every corner, from the slides to the delightful rustic Polynesian coconut salad! The Director of Mana Bay, Sasheen Akbani, spills the tropical tea: Mana Bay is not just a waterpark; it&#8217;s your tropical escape to create Insta-worthy moments. Live, laugh, and love while soaking up the good vibes – that&#8217;s the Mana Bay promise!</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Spread across a whopping 60,000 sq. metres, Mana Bay proudly wears the crown as South Asia&#8217;s third-largest waterpark. Feeling adventurous? Dive into the thrill rides, chill in the cabanas, or pamper yourself with spa moments. It is a one-stop-shop entertainment destination! With 17 rides, 4 attractions, 11 food havens, and 18 cabanas, Mana Bay is not just an adventure hub, it is your secret oasis in the concrete desert offering the biggest manmade beach in the country with a stunning volcano view. Need more? How about a 700-metre-long Lazy River named &#8220;Enchanted Waters,&#8221; waves that will make you feel like floating and the first-ever double Flowrider in the country!</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">For the young voyagers, KidzKraze is a mini-paradise filled with water cannons, slides, and giggles. Because at Mana Bay, the fun does not stop – it is a playground where everyone is invited! Eager for a culinary escapade? Mana Bay offers 11 delectable dining destinations, comprising seven restaurants and four food trucks. Whether you are a culinary explorer or on the hunt for delightful snacks, the fusion of international and Polynesian flavours will elevate your palate to new heights. It&#8217;s a must for any gastronomic journey! Imagine a day out with friends or family at Mana Bay — your perfect getaway to unwind and rejuvenate. So, grab your sun hat, slather on the sunscreen, and let Mana Bay sprinkle a dash of magic on your bucket list!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/mana-bay-dive-into-an-aquatic-wonder-just-a-splash-away/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korea’s Two New Visa Programmes Know What It Means For Indian Tourists</title>
		<link>/south-koreas-two-new-visa-programmes-know-what-it-means-for-indian-tourists/</link>
					<comments>/south-koreas-two-new-visa-programmes-know-what-it-means-for-indian-tourists/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea’s Two New Visa Programmes Know What It Means For Indian Tourists]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=509</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[South Korea is responding to the global interest in its culture, driven by the success...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">South Korea is responding to the global interest in its culture, driven by the success of K-pop and K-dramas, by introducing two new visas in 2024—the digital nomad visa (workation visa) and the K-culture training visa (Hallyu visa). The goal is to attract millions of foreign tourists this year, and transform South Korea into a preferred international tourist destination. If reports are to go by, South Korea is implementing reforms to streamline travel within the country. The introduction of foreign mobile payments and a traveler mobility app aims to facilitate shopping and easy transportation for international visitors. English versions of navigation systems are also in the works. All these will collectively contribute to South Korea&#8217;s vision of offering a more accessible and enjoyable experience for tourists.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">South Korea recently introduced the workation visa that encourages extended stays for foreign nationals. This visa combines work and travel, allowing visitors to stay for up to one year, in contrast to the 90-day limit on tourist visas. To qualify, applicants need one year of work experience in their industry, affiliated with international companies. The visa is open to families, except for children turning 18 or older, and requires applicants to earn double South Korea&#8217;s gross national product, maintain personal medical insurance, and secure home evacuation coverage exceeding 100 million won ($7,750) in case of emergencies.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Workation visa holders cannot engage in profit-making activities or work for local companies as it requires a separate visa for such endeavors. Applications can be submitted at Korean Embassies, and visa changes are possible for those on limited stays who meet necessary conditions. South Korea’s Hallyu visa or the K-culture training visa will allow foreign individuals enrolled in cultural academies to stay for a maximum of two years. The visa aims to provide candidates who are passionate about Korean culture, K-pop, and related fields, with firsthand knowledge from experts in Korean music, drama, film, animation, and gaming industries.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">This extensive, hands-on training program offers insight into the inner workings of the Korean entertainment scene and content creation. The Hallyu visa, unlike the E-6 visa, which requires trainee contracts with Korean entertainment firms, simplifies the process by requiring applicants to register at approved Korean institutes under the Ministry of Culture, Sports, and Tourism.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/south-koreas-two-new-visa-programmes-know-what-it-means-for-indian-tourists/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Evidence of world’s Oldest Forest Found In New York US</title>
		<link>/evidence-of-worlds-oldest-forest-found-in-new-york-us/</link>
					<comments>/evidence-of-worlds-oldest-forest-found-in-new-york-us/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evidence of world’s Oldest Forest Found In New York US]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=506</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A groundbreaking discovery has been made in a deserted quarry near Cairo, New York, where...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">A groundbreaking discovery has been made in a deserted quarry near Cairo, New York, where researchers from the University of Binghamton in the US and the University of Cardiff in Wales have unearthed the planet&#8217;s most ancient forest. The fossils, embedded in rocks dating back a staggering 385 million years, provide a unique window into Earth&#8217;s distant past. It is estimated that the forest once covered an area of approximately 400 km. If reports are to go by, this forest predates the Amazon rainforest and Japan’s Yakushima Forest, which are some of the oldest forests in the world we know today.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Through several studies conducted by palaeobotanists on the petrified roots found embedded in the region’s rocks, it was declared that this is Earth&#8217;s oldest known forest. This incredible discovery unfolds the history of a time that existed long before human existence. Think of the time of dinosaurs when you think about this forest. Another thing about this forest that baffled researchers is the fact that, unlike their contemporary counterparts, the ancient trees of this forest didn’t propagate through the release of seeds. They in fact, relied on spores for reproduction. This unique characteristic adds a fascinating layer to our understanding of prehistoric ecosystems. It’s interesting to note that fungi share a similar method of reproduction.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">As researchers continue to delve into the secrets preserved in the rocks near Cairo, New York, this discovery promises to deepen our understanding of Earth&#8217;s early ecosystems, offering a glimpse into the fascinating world of ancient plants and the processes that shaped our planet over millions of years.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Other ancient woodlands that still exist are Daintree Rainforest in Australia that date back over 180 million years, Tasmania&#8217;s Tarkine Rainforest is over 65 million years old, Bialowieza Forest in Poland has been around for more than 8000 years, Sequoia National Park in the United States is home to the giant sequoia trees, some of which have stood for over 3,000 years. India’s Western Ghats ranges are also home to freshwater swamp forests that date back millions of years. It’s easy to fall in love with these ancient forests that not only capture the beauty of bygone eras but also serve as invaluable reservoirs of Earth’s history.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/evidence-of-worlds-oldest-forest-found-in-new-york-us/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Plan Your Gulmarg And Leh Trips For Khelo India Winter Games 2024</title>
		<link>/plan-your-gulmarg-and-leh-trips-for-khelo-india-winter-games-2024/</link>
					<comments>/plan-your-gulmarg-and-leh-trips-for-khelo-india-winter-games-2024/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Plan Your Gulmarg And Leh Trips For Khelo India Winter Games 2024]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=503</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Come February 2, 2024, Gulmarg, Kashmir, will be hosting the fourth edition of the much-awaited...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Come February 2, 2024, Gulmarg, Kashmir, will be hosting the fourth edition of the much-awaited Khelo India Winter Games. If reports are to go by, all concerned departments are working to ensure all facilities meet international standards. As per the reports, the success of past editions has helped transform Jammu and Kashmir into a winter sports hub. Sports in India are more than cricket. And keeping this in mind, the Khelo India initiative was launched by the Ministry of Youth Affairs and Sports. Ever since its launch in 2021, Khelo India has been a game-changer, fostering a culture of sports and fitness across the country. While the summer edition of Khelo India has gained widespread recognition, the Winter Games component is slowly carving its niche, bringing forth not only the hidden talents in winter sports, but also the destinations associated with it.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The Khelo India Winter Games focuses on sports like ice hockey, cross-country, skiing, and snowboarding. Interestingly, though the northern states like Jammu and Kashmir, Himachal Pradesh, and Uttarakhand naturally have a stronghold in winter sports, several athletes from states that are not traditionally associated with cold weather sports have been making their mark. The Winter Games encompass a variety of disciplines. Ice hockey, cross-country, skiing and snowboarding in particular have been tremendously impressive. It’s not just sports enthusiasts, but travellers from all over India and abroad have made it to the games to witness the adrenaline-pumping sports.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Khelo India Winter Games is also a great opportunity to showcase the rich culture and warm hospitality of the Union Territories of Jammu and Kashmir and Ladakh. As per the Sports Authority of India (SAI), the 4th Edition of Khelo India Winter Games 2024 will be held from February 2 to 6, 2024, in two Union Territories of Jammu &amp; Kashmir and Ladakh. The event will feature competitions across seven sports, and with participation from 860 athletes, in two venues – Gulmarg and Leh. At the moment, Gulmarg is experiencing a snowless winter which makes one wonder about the winter games. But one can still hope for the much-awaited (and timely) snow in Gulmarg for the exciting Khelo India Winter Games.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/plan-your-gulmarg-and-leh-trips-for-khelo-india-winter-games-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>22-million-year-old Lost Forest Resurfaces In Panama Canal</title>
		<link>/22-million-year-old-lost-forest-resurfaces-in-panama-canal/</link>
					<comments>/22-million-year-old-lost-forest-resurfaces-in-panama-canal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[22-million-year-old Lost Forest Resurfaces In Panama Canal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=500</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a remarkable discovery, scientists have unearthed a mysterious long-lost world that reportedly disappeared from...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">In a remarkable discovery, scientists have unearthed a mysterious long-lost world that reportedly disappeared from Earth by a volcanic eruption approximately 22 million years ago. The rediscovery took place in the Panama Canal, where researchers from the Smithsonian Tropical Research Institute stumbled upon a lost forest on Barro Colorado Island, revealing that it harbours a species now absent from our planet. The vast mangrove forest at Barro Colorado Island, a peculiar find by the scientific team, offers a glimpse into a bygone era. This discovery will take you back to the Miocene Epoch, around 23 million years ago, when the South American and Caribbean plates collided, shaping the topography of present-day Panama and Central America.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Following this geological collision, a gradual transformation occurred, leading from a mound to a hill, and eventually giving rise to an island in the vast oceanic expanse — Barro Colorado Island.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Facebook Twitter Pinterest</strong><br />
Its periphery is dotted with towering trees, reaching impressive heights of up to 130 ft, forming a lush forest. Examinations of sedimentary samples from the island proved instrumental for the scientists. They found out that the area provided an ideal habitat for an ancient species of mangroves, excluding the presence of other tree varieties. The unique ecological system was the reason behind the forest&#8217;s origin in regions where fresh and marine water intermingled. Notably, during the Miocene Epoch, atmospheric carbon dioxide concentration soared significantly higher than contemporary levels, estimated to be at least 500 ppmv (parts per million by volume), in contrast to today&#8217;s approximately 400 ppmv. This heightened concentration facilitated the growth of these ancient mangroves to towering dimensions unparalleled by their present-day counterparts.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Read more: How to click the best pics while on a trip? Tips and tricks</strong><br />
The team, delving into the scientific intricacies of their discovery, unearthed 121 preserved pieces of wood in a Barro Colorado Island stream. They christened this ancient mangrove species Sonneratioxylon barrocoloradoensis. The genus, Sonneratioxylon, pays homage to the existing group of species, while the latter part of the name acknowledges the island of its origin. Interestingly, although this mangrove species has distant relatives in contemporary Southeast Asia, the lack of other tree fossils near the island suggests the challenges other species faced in surviving there.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>22-million-year-old lost forest resurfaces in Panama Canal!</strong><br />
Fossil evidence has offered an explanation of the mangrove forest&#8217;s disappearance, pointing to a volcanic eruption as the reason behind its extinction. This eruption triggered a ‘lahar,’ an Indonesian term referring to an aggressive flow of water, mud, rocks, and ash. Lahars, akin to a swift and expansive blanket of wet concrete, have a remarkable ability to cover large areas almost instantaneously. Their silica-rich waters, coupled with rapid flow, played a pivotal role in preserving fossils. The concrete-like blanket prevented decomposition, allowing the waters to seep into the tissues of living organisms and leaving plants and animals with no opportunity to rot. This rediscovered ancient world at Barro Colorado Island not only offers a glimpse into a prehistoric ecosystem, but also explains how the interplay of geological forces and catastrophic events have shaped Earth&#8217;s history.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/22-million-year-old-lost-forest-resurfaces-in-panama-canal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
