<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Evidence of world’s Oldest Forest Found In New York US &#8211; Quebecnacabeca</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/evidence-of-worlds-oldest-forest-found-in-new-york-us/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 14:43:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/live-favicon.jpg</url>
	<title>Evidence of world’s Oldest Forest Found In New York US &#8211; Quebecnacabeca</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Evidence of world’s Oldest Forest Found In New York US</title>
		<link>/evidence-of-worlds-oldest-forest-found-in-new-york-us/</link>
					<comments>/evidence-of-worlds-oldest-forest-found-in-new-york-us/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evidence of world’s Oldest Forest Found In New York US]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=506</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A groundbreaking discovery has been made in a deserted quarry near Cairo, New York, where...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">A groundbreaking discovery has been made in a deserted quarry near Cairo, New York, where researchers from the University of Binghamton in the US and the University of Cardiff in Wales have unearthed the planet&#8217;s most ancient forest. The fossils, embedded in rocks dating back a staggering 385 million years, provide a unique window into Earth&#8217;s distant past. It is estimated that the forest once covered an area of approximately 400 km. If reports are to go by, this forest predates the Amazon rainforest and Japan’s Yakushima Forest, which are some of the oldest forests in the world we know today.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Through several studies conducted by palaeobotanists on the petrified roots found embedded in the region’s rocks, it was declared that this is Earth&#8217;s oldest known forest. This incredible discovery unfolds the history of a time that existed long before human existence. Think of the time of dinosaurs when you think about this forest. Another thing about this forest that baffled researchers is the fact that, unlike their contemporary counterparts, the ancient trees of this forest didn’t propagate through the release of seeds. They in fact, relied on spores for reproduction. This unique characteristic adds a fascinating layer to our understanding of prehistoric ecosystems. It’s interesting to note that fungi share a similar method of reproduction.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">As researchers continue to delve into the secrets preserved in the rocks near Cairo, New York, this discovery promises to deepen our understanding of Earth&#8217;s early ecosystems, offering a glimpse into the fascinating world of ancient plants and the processes that shaped our planet over millions of years.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Other ancient woodlands that still exist are Daintree Rainforest in Australia that date back over 180 million years, Tasmania&#8217;s Tarkine Rainforest is over 65 million years old, Bialowieza Forest in Poland has been around for more than 8000 years, Sequoia National Park in the United States is home to the giant sequoia trees, some of which have stood for over 3,000 years. India’s Western Ghats ranges are also home to freshwater swamp forests that date back millions of years. It’s easy to fall in love with these ancient forests that not only capture the beauty of bygone eras but also serve as invaluable reservoirs of Earth’s history.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/evidence-of-worlds-oldest-forest-found-in-new-york-us/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
