<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>South Korea’s Two New Visa Programmes Know What It Means For Indian Tourists &#8211; Quebecnacabeca</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/south-koreas-two-new-visa-programmes-know-what-it-means-for-indian-tourists/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 14:42:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/live-favicon.jpg</url>
	<title>South Korea’s Two New Visa Programmes Know What It Means For Indian Tourists &#8211; Quebecnacabeca</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>South Korea’s Two New Visa Programmes Know What It Means For Indian Tourists</title>
		<link>/south-koreas-two-new-visa-programmes-know-what-it-means-for-indian-tourists/</link>
					<comments>/south-koreas-two-new-visa-programmes-know-what-it-means-for-indian-tourists/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea’s Two New Visa Programmes Know What It Means For Indian Tourists]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=509</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[South Korea is responding to the global interest in its culture, driven by the success...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">South Korea is responding to the global interest in its culture, driven by the success of K-pop and K-dramas, by introducing two new visas in 2024—the digital nomad visa (workation visa) and the K-culture training visa (Hallyu visa). The goal is to attract millions of foreign tourists this year, and transform South Korea into a preferred international tourist destination. If reports are to go by, South Korea is implementing reforms to streamline travel within the country. The introduction of foreign mobile payments and a traveler mobility app aims to facilitate shopping and easy transportation for international visitors. English versions of navigation systems are also in the works. All these will collectively contribute to South Korea&#8217;s vision of offering a more accessible and enjoyable experience for tourists.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">South Korea recently introduced the workation visa that encourages extended stays for foreign nationals. This visa combines work and travel, allowing visitors to stay for up to one year, in contrast to the 90-day limit on tourist visas. To qualify, applicants need one year of work experience in their industry, affiliated with international companies. The visa is open to families, except for children turning 18 or older, and requires applicants to earn double South Korea&#8217;s gross national product, maintain personal medical insurance, and secure home evacuation coverage exceeding 100 million won ($7,750) in case of emergencies.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Workation visa holders cannot engage in profit-making activities or work for local companies as it requires a separate visa for such endeavors. Applications can be submitted at Korean Embassies, and visa changes are possible for those on limited stays who meet necessary conditions. South Korea’s Hallyu visa or the K-culture training visa will allow foreign individuals enrolled in cultural academies to stay for a maximum of two years. The visa aims to provide candidates who are passionate about Korean culture, K-pop, and related fields, with firsthand knowledge from experts in Korean music, drama, film, animation, and gaming industries.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">This extensive, hands-on training program offers insight into the inner workings of the Korean entertainment scene and content creation. The Hallyu visa, unlike the E-6 visa, which requires trainee contracts with Korean entertainment firms, simplifies the process by requiring applicants to register at approved Korean institutes under the Ministry of Culture, Sports, and Tourism.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/south-koreas-two-new-visa-programmes-know-what-it-means-for-indian-tourists/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
