<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Plan Your Gulmarg And Leh Trips For Khelo India Winter Games 2024 &#8211; Quebecnacabeca</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/plan-your-gulmarg-and-leh-trips-for-khelo-india-winter-games-2024/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 14:43:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/live-favicon.jpg</url>
	<title>Plan Your Gulmarg And Leh Trips For Khelo India Winter Games 2024 &#8211; Quebecnacabeca</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Plan Your Gulmarg And Leh Trips For Khelo India Winter Games 2024</title>
		<link>/plan-your-gulmarg-and-leh-trips-for-khelo-india-winter-games-2024/</link>
					<comments>/plan-your-gulmarg-and-leh-trips-for-khelo-india-winter-games-2024/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 14:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Plan Your Gulmarg And Leh Trips For Khelo India Winter Games 2024]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=503</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Come February 2, 2024, Gulmarg, Kashmir, will be hosting the fourth edition of the much-awaited...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Come February 2, 2024, Gulmarg, Kashmir, will be hosting the fourth edition of the much-awaited Khelo India Winter Games. If reports are to go by, all concerned departments are working to ensure all facilities meet international standards. As per the reports, the success of past editions has helped transform Jammu and Kashmir into a winter sports hub. Sports in India are more than cricket. And keeping this in mind, the Khelo India initiative was launched by the Ministry of Youth Affairs and Sports. Ever since its launch in 2021, Khelo India has been a game-changer, fostering a culture of sports and fitness across the country. While the summer edition of Khelo India has gained widespread recognition, the Winter Games component is slowly carving its niche, bringing forth not only the hidden talents in winter sports, but also the destinations associated with it.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The Khelo India Winter Games focuses on sports like ice hockey, cross-country, skiing, and snowboarding. Interestingly, though the northern states like Jammu and Kashmir, Himachal Pradesh, and Uttarakhand naturally have a stronghold in winter sports, several athletes from states that are not traditionally associated with cold weather sports have been making their mark. The Winter Games encompass a variety of disciplines. Ice hockey, cross-country, skiing and snowboarding in particular have been tremendously impressive. It’s not just sports enthusiasts, but travellers from all over India and abroad have made it to the games to witness the adrenaline-pumping sports.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Khelo India Winter Games is also a great opportunity to showcase the rich culture and warm hospitality of the Union Territories of Jammu and Kashmir and Ladakh. As per the Sports Authority of India (SAI), the 4th Edition of Khelo India Winter Games 2024 will be held from February 2 to 6, 2024, in two Union Territories of Jammu &amp; Kashmir and Ladakh. The event will feature competitions across seven sports, and with participation from 860 athletes, in two venues – Gulmarg and Leh. At the moment, Gulmarg is experiencing a snowless winter which makes one wonder about the winter games. But one can still hope for the much-awaited (and timely) snow in Gulmarg for the exciting Khelo India Winter Games.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/plan-your-gulmarg-and-leh-trips-for-khelo-india-winter-games-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
